[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
[Arnaldo] Thank you
for your loyal service.
[gunshot]
[Julio] Now, where is that witch,
Helena Montoya?!
I am going to kill her!
And if she survives, I'll kill her again.
-[Camia] Lily, it's an ambush!
-[Helena] Shoot them, baby girl!
-Shoot them!
-Mama!
-[screams]
-[gunfire]
[Julio] This is your destiny.
You know why?
It's because you messed
with the wrong Ardiente.
You messed with me.
Mama!
[Julio] Lily Cruz was the one
who planted the bomb
in your mother's ambulance.
Lily Cruz was the one who killed her.
Did you hear that, Mama?
Papa said he'd avenge you.
My father made so many mistakes.
But on his behalf, I hope
one day you can forgive him.
I can't forgive him
because he's the reason this all started.
Raul saved me, Lily. I'm grateful to Raul.
So, we should try to forgive him.
I'm turning myself in.
I will pay for my crimes,
so I can be worthy of your love.
I hope you can wait for me, Camia.
I'll wait for you, Damian.
[Diego] Dad, your longtime dream
is finally coming true.
Arnaldo and I will live as a family now.
We love you very much.
Stop the funeral!
Stop the funeral! Get out of my way!
Step aside! Let me through!
I'll bury my husband myself!
Stop the funeral!
Get out of here!
I will bury my own husband!
Emilia, that's enough.
-Get out of here!
-Don't make a scene!
Out!
I'm his wife so I should
bury him myself! Now get lost!
Ma, what are you doing?
Show Dad some respect.
How dare you go against your own mother?!
Did you hit your head again?
Want me to tell everyone
the truth about you?!
-Huh?! You want that?!
-Emilia! Stop it!
Why, Papa? Is everything my fault again?!
Will you kick me out
of my own husband's burial?
My husband's bastard son
should leave, not me!
And you! You killed my mother!
And you! You're just his wannabe mistress!
It's you who shouldn't be here! Get lost!
Don't blame us for what you did, Emilia!
I saw how you were the one who shot Raul.
I didn't kill him. I loved my husband.
Now, get out of my sight! Get lost!
Don't you dare hurt my mother!
We didn't kill Raul, you did!
Go to hell!
Do you really want to bury your husband?
Fine. Then go rest in peace!
[crowd screams]
Get me out of here!
Let's go. Mom! Come on, Mom.
-Excuse us. Let us through!
-Help!
[grunting]
What did I tell you?
You keep picking fights
you can't even win.
Look at you!
You! Help her.
-Help! Faster!
-Get her out of there.
[sobs]
[yelps]
What the hell was that?
You are so dumb! You're stupid!
You know, I'm running
out of derogatory words
to explain your stupidity.
Hey, I'm not dumb! I'm smart!
-Hold that woman down. Now.
-Let go of me! Let go!
You think you're smart, don't you?
What did you do there, huh?
You made a laughingstock out of yourself!
You fell into the grave
because of your nonsense.
You couldn't even defend yourself.
Not only that, you even
put Arnaldo in danger.
You're going to blow his cover!
Do you realize what Lily Cruz
could do to him
once she learns that he's a spy?
You might just have to bury your son next!
You want that? You want that for Arnaldo?
Grandpa, I think Mama isn't
thinking clearly anymore.
We better go before
Lily suspects something.
You're right.
-Hey, stop--Hold her down!
-Let go of me!
-Don't let her go.
-Hold her. Get her in the car.
Get her in the car.
Come on, get her inside.
-Go!
-[Emilia screams]
I hate you!
[Emilia sobs]
Stupid.
Let go of me! I'm not crazy!
Papa, why are you taking me here?
Please hold her down.
Wait, Papa. I don't belong here.
Stop it! Let go of me! Stop this!
Let go of me! Hey!
Why are you bringing me here?
Mama's going to get mad once she finds out
that you brought me here.
She'll tear you to pieces.
This is what's best for us, Emilia.
Your lunacy isn't doing us
any good anymore.
How could you do this to me,
Papa? Let go of me!
Take that woman inside. Take her inside!
[screams]
Let go of me!
Stop it! You're all going to regret this.
Hey, let go of me! You too!
Papa!
Papa, don't do this to me!
I don't deserve to be here!
Mama. Come on, please do something.
Look at what Papa's doing to me!
Mama, please!
Raul?
Raul, can you please--Raul.
Don't just stand there.
Do something!
What?!
Mama. Why am I here?
I don't deserve to be here, right?
Come on, Mama.
Raul? Raul, please.
Please, Raul.
Papa's at it again!
He's always doing this to me.
Grandpa, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Arnaldo, listen to me
and listen to me well.
We can't rely on your mother anymore.
It's just the two of us now.
It's up to us to reclaim
our family's lost glory.
Okay. But how are we going to do that?
We lost a lot
since the kidnapping
turned into a major disaster.
Forget the kidnapping.
What matters is that we will be able
to take over Red Dragon's syndicate.
That's the only way
for us to recover our lost power.
For us to get more men,
secure more weapons,
more than enough money, and protection.
And your grandma's syndicate
could provide all that.
That's exactly what we need.
All right. I'm all in.
But you have to promise me one thing.
Lily Cruz is mine.
She's going to be my slave,
and I want Diego dead.
You understand?
Help me, then.
Help me get your grandma's fortune,
and I promise you,
I will give you Lily Cruz
and Diego on a silver platter.
[ominous music swelling]
Lily Cruz had my wife
and daughter kidnapped.
And two members of my family
died because of them.
My daughter, Emilia,
did not kill her husband, Raul.
Lily Cruz killed Raul and Helena.
Helena died while trying
to save our daughter, Emilia.
She died a hero.
But Lily Cruz?
She's the real Red Dragon.
She's the real criminal!
And I swear by the name
of my beloved, Helena.
Helena, if you're listening up in heaven…
I promise you that I won't stop
until that criminal, Lily Cruz,
pays for all her crimes.
Governor, what do you have
to say about Jaguar's claim
that you were part
of Red Dragon's syndicate?
And that you allegedly had Lily Cruz
and her mother kidnapped?
These are all lies.
Let's just see
who the people will believe.
A criminal like Damian,
or their trusted Governor Julio?
And there he goes again.
Lying straight to our faces.
Hey! Stop badmouthing the Ardientes.
Why? I'm telling the truth.
If someone hears you,
they might have you kidnapped.
Do you want to end up like Lily Cruz?
Mr. Damian, what can you say?
Mr. Damian, please give us a statement.
Don't believe Julio Ardiente.
I am the Jaguar.
I used to work for Red Dragon.
I know what really happened.
Who is the real Red Dragon,
Helena Montoya or Lily Cruz?
Helena Montoya was Red Dragon.
She had control over the syndicates
and connections to the Triad.
She also worked with the Ardientes.
They were the ones who
kidnapped Lily and Camia Cruz.
Damian Cruz, why did you turn yourself in?
I surrendered because I don't
want to hurt the people I love.
They've given me countless chances.
I don't want to disappoint them again.
I will get my life together
because I want to be worthy
of the love they have shown me.
[tense music playing]
Helena died while trying
to save our daughter, Emilia.
She died a hero. But Lily Cruz?
She's the real Red Dragon.
She's the real criminal!
Helena, if you're listening up in heaven,
I promise you that I won't stop
until that criminal, Lily Cruz,
pays for all her crimes.
Lily…
Mom.
I just found out that Julio
had Emilia sent to a psychiatric ward.
[chuckles]
That's where that woman belongs.
And I'm not surprised, Mom.
Because all the Ardientes are insane.
So, that's why Emilia wasn't
at the press conference.
[scoffs]
Can you believe it?
Julio was able to do that
to his own daughter.
Julio Ardiente? I expect nothing less.
The Ardientes don't care about family.
And I have a strong feeling
that Julio had something to do
with Helena's death.
Now, the question is…
Who's helping him take over
Red Dragon's position in the syndicate?
[ominous music playing]
Arnaldo!
For tonight's entertainment.
My Lily Cruz. Choose.
-What do you want? This one?
-Let me go.
This one? No. I'll pick.
[yelps]
You want it? Tell me you want more.
-Want more?
-You bastard!
Yes! Yes!
-You love me?
-No, I don't love you!
-You love me!
Here's more!
Don't come near me.
Arnaldo!
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
How dare you go against your own mother?!
Did you hit your head again?
Want me to tell everyone
the truth about you?! Huh?!
-You want that?!
-Emilia! Stop it!
Why, Papa? Is everything my fault again?!
Will you kick me out of
my own husband's burial?
The real Arnaldo's back.
He's the one helping Julio.
Diego.
When will all this end?
I really thought Arnaldo changed.
What next? I have nothing left.
They've already taken
everything away from me.
No. I'm here.
I'm still here.
We are all here for you.
We're your family now, Diego.
Lily, come with me.
Let's run away from here. Far away.
Let's fulfill our dreams.
I want to be a father and a husband.
I want us to start our
own family and live in peace.
Lily, now's our chance
to finally be happy.
[car honks]
[soft instrumental playing]
Well. Our house hasn't changed.
[Julio chuckles]
It hasn't changed at all.
Just like the way we left it.
You smell that?
Ah, the scent of power.
[chuckles]
Well, it's good to be home.
This place was where I shaped
who you'd become.
This is where I shaped you to be a ruler.
So, it's only fitting that this is where
the Ardiente family should start over.
And in no time, we will reign
over this town again.
Well, if that is the case,
I better get going.
I'm meeting with Lily.
I must find out if our enemies
are planning something against you again.
So, you mean to tell me
that you know
where Lily Cruz's new house is?
Yes. It wasn't that hard to find.
[chuckles]
You know, I don't think
they're hiding from us.
I think they've accepted the fact
that they can never escape us.
Perhaps they're running away
from the nightmares
they had in their old house because of us.
Well, I guess it's time we tormented them
with a new nightmare.
Don't you agree?
Okay.
Just be careful at all times, Arnaldo.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
I cannot afford anything bad
Understand?
Viva Ardiente.
[soft instrumental playing]
Put all the luggage in the trunk, okay?
We have to leave before anyone sees us.
[ominous music playing]
Let's go.
Ma'am, where are we going again?
To the St. Monica chapel in Rosario.
Lily has strictly ordered us not to
let anyone know we're leaving.
How come?
I have no idea. Shall we?
-Okay.
-Let's go.
[ominous music playing]
Well, hello there.
What are you guys up to?
Governor, your visitors are here.
Hello, ladies.
Please sit down.
Ah, Jenny, could you prepare us
some hors d'oeuvres
and a bottle of wine?
Oh, I didn't get your name.
-Cris.
-Hello, Cris.
So, you want to take control
of Red Dragon's syndicate?
Yes. I'd like to get her money,
her resources,
her arms…
All her businesses.
With all due respect, Governor,
but what's in it for us?
The Ardientes are ruined.
You're running out of men
and what's left of your funds.
The only thing you have left
is your position.
Don't underestimate my position, Cris.
I'm still the governor of this province.
Now, let's look at the other side.
Let's take a look at your group.
The other syndicates are slowly
starting to consume you.
And I'm aware that the police
are on your tail.
You're like frightened little mice
scurrying blind all over the place.
What you need now
is a new leader to lead your syndicate.
And I'm the only one who can do that.
So, you see?
You need me as much as I need you.
No deal.
If you want to take over
Red Dragon's group,
we aren't the ones
you should be talking to.
Then, who?
The lords of the syndicate.
[laughs]
So, there's someone higher than Helena?
The Triad.
[tense music playing]
We can only allow one companion
for Governor Ardiente.
Stay here, I'll go with him.
[ominous music playing]
Jepoy?
-Ma'am?
-I think we're being followed.
Is it Julio's men?
We have to lose them, Jepoy. Hurry.
All right. Hold on.
You can't run from me.
[ominous music playing]
Jepoy, they're still behind us.
We need to lose them.
[tense music playing]
Jepoy, watch out for that truck!
[tires screeching]
Hey! Watch where you're going!
What did you say?!
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
No!
[breathing heavily]
You can run, but you can't hide.
I'll find out what you're up to.
Governor Julio Ardiente.
Stefano dela Torre.
I represent the Triad.
I assure you the whole province
of Ardiente
will be under my control
if I can take over
Helena Montoya's organization.
[scoffs]
And what makes you think
we'll hand it over to you?
Well, I am the only ally
of Helena in Ardiente.
So, it's only right
that I take over her syndicate
in my province.
Then give me the password.
What?
If you and Red Dragon really were allies,
then she would've given you
the password already.
Where's my daughter?
She asked me to give you this, ma'am.
-Huh?
-To all of you.
For you to gain access
to the Triad's database.
Or perhaps, she only toyed with you,
the same way she deceived other
politicians and businessmen.
Without the password,
I cannot give you the resources
and the protection
that you are asking for.
And without the password…
We cannot trust you.
Good day, Governor Ardiente.
Mom?
Lily!
Lily, Diego, what's this?
Mom.
Starting tomorrow, I will be Diego's wife.
We're getting married.
Oh, Lily!
We've prepared your suits and dresses.
I'm so happy for you both. Finally!
[Stefano] If you and Red Dragon
really were allies,
then she would've given you
the password already.
For you to gain access
to the Triad's database.
Or perhaps, she only toyed with you,
the same way she deceived other
politicians and businessmen.
Without the password,
I cannot give you the resources
and the protection
that you are asking for.
You can't deceive me, Helena.
A woman can never deceive me.
Colonel.
You're all set, Governor.
You can go inside now.
-Colonel, wait for me here.
-Yes, Governor.
[humming]
Hi, Papa. Look. I'm practicing the piano.
Emilia.
That's enough.
Your mother's dead.
That's not true, Papa.
Mama just told me
that she's on her way here.
You know, she's going to see me
because she misses me so much.
It sounds like you
and your mother really bonded.
Of course, Papa.
In that short time,
I really felt loved, Papa.
Mama really loves me.
She gave me almost everything.
Money, power, everything, Papa.
But more importantly, the trust.
So, I really feel that,
you know, Mama loves me.
[humming]
Did she ever mention to you
about the syndicate?
Yes, she told me that I would inherit it.
Because I'm the heiress to the throne.
[humming]
Did she give you the Triad's password?
Emilia.
I need that password,
so I can take over
your mother's syndicate.
[tense music playing]
[humming frantically]
Emilia, please stop it!
-Stop it!
-Ah!
-Papa, what are you doing?
-Give me the password!
Give me the password!
-Ow!
-Give it to me!
[sobbing]
Diego?
Why are you still here?
LI'L BRO, WHAT'S UP?
What do you feel about this?
Are you feeling guilty that
you didn't invite Arnaldo?
Lily, what if we're wrong?
What if Arnaldo really has changed?
So, you're willing to risk
our lives for him?
Are you really willing
to risk our dreams, Diego?
I'm willing to give up everything for you.
I love you.
Hey!
-Oh, my.
-Mom.
Look at you two.
The bride and groom mustn't see each other
the night before the wedding.
That's bad luck, you know?
Sorry, Mom. It's Diego's fault.
He didn't want to go inside just yet.
Auntie, I can't wait.
I'm so excited to start
my new life with my wife.
Diego, just a little longer.
And all your dreams will come true.
-Just a bit more.
-It'll happen tomorrow.
-Now, go on. Go on inside.
-You heard your fiancée.
All right.
But where's my good night kiss?
In front of my mom? Are you serious?
Tomorrow, then. Good night.
-Good night kiss.
-Still trying to score.
I still don't have any updates
on Lily and Diego.
But if my hunch is right,
they're planning something against you.
Well, I want you to take care of that.
Because my plate is full.
Your mom's weirdness and incompetence
are the roots of all my problems.
I don't know. I think she was born
to be a total pain in the neck.
I've got a migraine.
-Grandpa.
-Yeah?
I need you to relax, okay?
Too much worrying is bad for your health.
I'll take care of it.
Arnaldo, I want to clear a path
for your comeback.
So that you can fulfill
all of your lifelong dreams.
And let's face it. Let's face the truth.
Age is creeping up on me.
I'm starting to feel it in my body.
I'm feeling it in my bones.
And I'm ready to turn over
the baton of leadership to you.
You know, I would be willing
to give up everything
just to see you lead this town
and continue our legacy,
the legacy of our family.
That is how it is going to be.
That is how the future will turn out.
But what they don't see is how
much you protect this family,
how you take care of us. How…
-How much you love me and Mama.
-That's true.
And in truth…
In truth, you are the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I want you to know that
I'll do everything in my power
to… protect you.
Take care of you.
Just a little longer,
I'll be the one
carrying on the family's legacy.
I promise you that.
That has always been my dream.
Thank you so much.
You know, Lily, your father always wanted
to walk you down the aisle
at your wedding.
But on one condition.
You'll only get married once you're forty.
[laughs]
Well, Dad, I'm sorry.
I'll get married thirteen years early.
Still, Lily.
I just know he's smiling
down on you right now.
Because you've found
your better half in Diego.
I hope so, Mom.
[laughs]
I want your men
to search Poblacion Ardiente
for a white van with this plate number.
And I want results
first thing in the morning.
Will do, Mayor.
Okay.
Let's go.
Arnaldo!
What took you so long?
I've been waiting so long
for you to visit me.
Hey, look. Those are my constituents.
Please say hi to them.
Look, it's the mayor.
Ah, sorry. I've been busy.
What happened to you? Tell me.
Your grandfather beat me up.
Why is he so cruel to me?
It's like I'm not his daughter.
Well, it's because you always
give him a hard time.
Listen.
I'll be gone for a while.
-You're leaving?
-Yeah.
I'm going to look for Lily and Diego.
So, it'll be just you
and Grandpa for a while.
But you have to promise me one thing.
Don't fight anymore.
Okay?
It's easy. Just give him what he wants.
And, just to give you a tip,
help him take over grandma's syndicate
and everything will be fine.
It's not fair. Your grandma
and papa already left me.
And now, you're leaving.
I'll be all alone.
Can you just stay, please?
Don't leave. Please.
I have to go.
I have to.
I'm really sorry I wasn't
a very good mother to you.
You could've been a great man
if only I'd just raised you properly.
But no matter what other people
say about us,
that our family's crazy,
or that we're evil,
believe me when I say
that I really love you.
And no one can question that.
I love you so much, son.
I love you too.
I love you too. I love you too.
[Emilia sobs]
I love you too, son.
My son. I love you so much.
I have to go.
Arnaldo.
Um, if you see your grandma and your papa,
can you please say hi to them for me?
Tell them I miss them so much.
You know, they're just
somewhere out there.
Huh?
[Emilia giggles]
Hey, hang that properly. It's crooked.
A little to the left.
A little more. There.
Good. Okay.
Now take the other paintings out with you.
[chuckles]
I won't allow this family's reign to end.
And you, Arnaldo, will continue my legacy.
You are the future of the Ardiente clan.
Live long, my son. Live long.
[Diego] Lily, no matter
how many times I fall,
no matter how many times I get hurt,
I'll never stop loving you.
Diego, you're the reason
I learned to love again.
Thank you for teaching me how to love.
We've tracked them down. In Rosario.
I offer you this ring
as a symbol of my eternal love
and faithfulness to you.
Wear this ring as a symbol
of my eternal love
and faithfulness to you.
[theme music playing]